export default {
    data: {
        "#2641D8": {
            "question": "Intrinsically Photosensitive Retinal Ganglion Cells in the eye are sensitive to",
            "answer": "Blue light",
            "options": ["Green light", "Red light", "Blue light", "Yellow light"]
        },
        "#358427": {
            "question": "Which is the oldest building material in Architecture?",
            "options": ["Wood", "Clay", "Calcium Carbonate", "Brick"],
            "answer": "Brick"
        },
        "#D62B2B": {
            "question": "During what period was Magnetic Compass used for navigation purposes",
            "answer": "1100 BC - 1200 BC",
            "options": ["1500 BC - 3500 BC", "1100 BC - 1200 BC", "800 BC - 900 BC", "500 BC - 700 BC"]
        },
        "#000000": {
            "question": "Homing pegions were used for courier services and Navigation during when",
            "answer": "From 1000 BC",
            "options": ["From 1000 BC", "From 2000 BC", "From 3000 BC", "From 4000 BC"]
        },
        "#7E726F": {
            "question": "Who is the creator and co-producer of the game Pointless?",
            "answer": "Richard Osman",
            "options": ["Richard Osman", "Chris Evans", "Chris Tarrant", "Carol Vorderman"]
        },
        "#7E8DD5": {
            "question": "Most popular food in America is Pizza, which is second most popular food?",
            "answer": "Oyster",
            "options": ["Burger", "Prawns", "Lasagne", "Oyster"]
        },
        "#396b63": {
            "question": "Which food has the highest protein?",
            "answer": "Egg White",
            "options": ["Milk", "Oat Meal", "Pork Chop", "Egg White", "Shrimp"]
        },
        "#30CFD0": {
            "question": "Which is the sixth Alkali Metal? Given five are Lithium, Sodium, Caesium, Francium, Potassium",
            "answer": "Rubidium",
            "options": ["Aluminium", "Rubidium", "Calcium", "Magnesium"]
        },
        "#7DCC27": {
            "question": "When was the period of Holocene Climatic Optimum (HCO)?",
            "answer": "8000 years BP (Before Present)",
            "options": ["500 years BP", "2000 years BP", "4000 years BP", "8000 years BP", "11000 years BP"]
        },
        "#C68327": {
            "question": "World's Deadiest Animals among these",
            "answer": "Freshwater Snail",
            "options": ["Freshwater Snail", "Ascaris Roundworm", "Hippopotamus", "Crocodile"]
        },
        "#7F27CA": {
            "question": "Who are the Top Three Coal Producers: United States, among these countries: Russian Federation, China, Indonesia, Australia, India, South Africa, Germany, Poland, Kazhakhistan?",
            "answer": "China, United States, India",
            "options": ["China, United States, Australia", "Russian Federation, Germany, Japan", "Russian Federation, Germany, South Africa", "China, United States, India", "United States, Russian Federation, China"]
        },
        "#7E8DD5": {
            "question": "Who is the leader in the Spa Industry?",
            "answer": "Europe",
            "options": ["Europe", "Latin America", "Asia Pacific", "North America", "Mid East Africa", "Africa"]
        },
        "#268B8F": {
            "question": "Largest expatriate population in GCC: Qatar, UAE, Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, Kuwait, Oman?",
            "answer": "Qatar, UAE: 85%",
            "options": ["Qatar, Saudi Arabia: 85%", "Kuwait, UAE: 85%", "Saudi Arabia, UAE: 85%", "Qatar, UAE: 85%", "Oman, UAE: 85%"]
        },
        "#C72882": {
            "question": "Most Earning Countries in World's Manufacturing Sector, among these countries: China, US, Japan, Korea, United Kingdom, Italy, Germany, France, Russia",
            "answer": "China, United States, Japan",
            "options": ["China, United States, United Kingdom", "China, United States, Japan", "United States, UK, Korea", "China,. Russia, United States", "United States, United Kingdom, Germany"]
        },
        "#7DD58E": {
            "question": "Top Countries with Highest Alcohol Addiction Rates",
            "answer": "Moldova",
            "options": ["Moldova", "Belarus", "Russia", "Estonia", "Romania", "Andorra", "Czech Republic", "Slovenia", "Ukraine", "Hungary"]
        },
        "#7E2D2D": {
            "question": "In the US, which age group reads the most as per recent statistics",
            "answer": "18-29",
            "options": ["18-29", "30-49", "50-64", "65+"]
        },
        "#D58D8D": {
            "question": "The hackers are arrested for breaking into U.S govt. and corporate computers and selling operating-system source code",
            "answer": "1989: The Germans and the KGB",
            "options": ["1990: Operation Sundevil", "1984: Hacker 'Zines", "1989: The Germans and the KGB", "1994: Hacking Tools R Us"]
        },
        "#26D744": {
            "question": "Vacuum Tubes dominated the electronics industry untill transistors were invented in 1947. In which year was the semiconductor invented?",
            "answer": "1958",
            "options": ["1958", "1960", "1962", "1964"]
        },
        "#362782": {
            "question": "What is the probability that people turn to online video for information?",
            "answer": "1 in 3",
            "question": ["1 in 3", "1 in 4", "1 in 5", "1 in 10"]
        },
        "#D542D7": {
            "question": "Which is the newest landmark that is seen from outer space?",
            "answer": "Colosseum",
            "question": ["Colosseum", "Uluru Rock", "The Kaaba", "Pyramids of Giza"]
        }
    }
}